Register to The Quincy Porter Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, Series I
  - Other Business, Financial, Legal Correspondence, I.G
    - Wheelock Signals, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 118)
      1958 May 13 -- typed letter signed
    - Yale Co-Operative Corporation (Box 10, Folder 118)
      1950 Mar 13 -- typed letter signed
    - Sandback, Helen K. to The Employers Group of Insurance Companies (Box 10, Folder 119)
      1960 Aug 11 -- typed letter (carbon)
  - Yaddo Papers, I.H
    - General Business, I.H.1
      - American Composers Alliance (Box 11, Folder 120)
        1938 Jul 20 -- typed letter signed [to E. Ames]
      - American Music Center, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 120)
        1940 Aug 29 -- typed letter (copy) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Ames, Elizabeth (Box 11, Folder 120-121)
        1938-1939 -- 2 autograph letters signed
        1937-1949 -- 25 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
        1950-1966 -- 10 typed letters signed
        1964 Jan 4 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
        1937-1966 -- 19 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
        No date -- 1 (typed copy of telegram) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Ames, Elizabeth to Richard Donovan (Box 11, Folder 122)
        1940-1965 -- 4 typed letters signed
        1963-1965 -- 7 typed letters (carbon)
      - The Associated Press (Box 11, Folder 123)
        1938 Aug 4 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
        7 typed letters (carbon)
      - Cohn, Arthur (Box 11, Folder 123)
        1938 Jun 20 -- typed letter signed
        1938 Jun 27 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 123)
        1938 -- 4 typed letters signed
        1938 -- 3 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - [Copland, Aaron] (Box 11, Folder 123)
      - Donovan, Richard (Box 11, Folder 124)
        1938-1940 -- 5 autograph letters signed
        [1947] -- autograph letter signed (copy)
        1938 Feb 1 -- typed letter signed
        1942 Apr 15 -- typed letter (copy)
        1938 -- 2 cards
        1940; No date -- 3 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
        1964 -- 2 typed letters (carbon) from Donovan to Elizabeth Ames
        1942 Apr 15 -- typed letter (carbon) from Donovan to David Frankenstein
        1942 May 4 -- typed letter (carbon) from Donovan to Bruno David Usher
        See also: Yaddo Music Committee
      - [Duke, John ?] (Box 11, Folder 124)
        No date -- autograph letter (incomplete)
      - Johansen, Gunnar (Box 11, Folder 125)
        1938 Jul 28 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Kirkpatrick, Ralph (Box 11, Folder 125)
        1933 -- 4 typed letters signed
        1938 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Luening, Otto (Box 11, Folder 125)
        1938 -- 6 typed letters signed
      - Moe, Henry Allen (Box 11, Folder 126)
      - National Broadcasting Co., Inc. (Box 11, Folder 126)
        1938 Aug 4 -- typed letter signed
        (notations by Quincy Porter)
      - National Orchestral Association (Box 11, Folder 126)
      - New York Herald Tribune (Box 11, Folder 126)
        1938 Jul 27 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Robetor, Jo Ann (Box 11, Folder 126)
        1938 Oct 17 -- typed letter signed
        1938 Aug 19 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Shepherd, Arthur (Box 11, Folder 126-127)
        1938 -- 6 autograph letters signed
        1938 -- 7 typed letters signed
        1938 Aug 20 -- typed letter
        1938 -- 3 telegrams
        1938 -- 4 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
        1937 Aug 27 -- 1 copy of telegram/letter to Quincy Porter
        No date -- 1 copy of telegram from Quincy Porter to Shepherd
      - Slade, John A. (Box 11, Folder 128)
        1963-1965 -- 3 typed letters signed
      - Starbuck, Kathryn H. (Box 11, Folder 128)
        1943 Apr 26 -- typed letter signed
        1945 Apr 17 -- typed letter
      - Waite, Marjorie Peabody (Box 11, Folder 128)
        1938-1941 -- 5 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      - WNYC (Municipal Broadcasting System, NY) (Box 11, Folder 128)
        1938-1939 -- 8 typed letters signed
        1938-1939 -- 3 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
        1938 Aug 30 -- typed letter (carbon) from WNYC to Benevolent Protective Musicians Association
      - Yaddo Music Committee (Box 11, Folder 129)
        1938 Jul 26 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
        1937-1938 -- 5 typed letters signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
        1937 Apr 25 -- typed letter from Quincy Porter to above
        1938 -- 5 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
        (various combinations of John Duke, Richard Donovan, Ralph Kirkpatrick, Arthur Shepherd, Otto Luening)
    - Prospective Yaddo Composers/Performers, I.H.2
      - Avery, Stanley R. (Box 11, Folder 130)
        1938 Jul 20 -- typed letter signed
        1938 Aug 31 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Barrows, John R. (Box 11, Folder 130)
        1938 Jun 15 -- card
      - Bashan, Leonard (Box 11, Folder 130)
        1947 Aug 7 -- typed letter signed
      - Beek, Sydney (Box 11, Folder 130)
        1938 Jun 23 -- typed letter signed
      - Berckman, Evelyn (Box 11, Folder 130)
        1938 Mar 9 -- typed letter signed
      - Bergen, Eugene (Box 11, Folder 130)
        1938 Jun 25 -- autograph letter signed
      - Beyer, Johanna M. (Box 11, Folder 130)
        1938 Aug 30 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Bodenhorn, Aaron (Box 11, Folder 130)
        [1938] -- 2 autograph letters signed
        [1938 ?] -- 2 rough copies, telegrams
      - Brant, Henry (Box 11, Folder 131)
      - Breul, Sue (Box 11, Folder 131)
      - Brown, Harold (Box 11, Folder 131)
        1938 May 2 -- typed letter [to Otto Luening, with notations by Otto Luening]
      - Brown, Northrop (Box 11, Folder 131)
      - Browning, Mortimer (Box 11, Folder 131)
        1938 Jul 8 -- autograph letter signed
        1938 Jul 19 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Brussels, Iris (Box 11, Folder 131)
        1938 Jul 15 -- typed letter signed
        1938 Jul 18 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Chanler, Theodore (Box 11, Folder 131)
        1938 Sep 8 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Cohn, Arthur (Box 11, Folder 131)
        1938 Jul 5 -- autograph letter signed
      - Conant, Harriet (Box 11, Folder 131)
      - Corzine, Cordi (Box 11, Folder 131)
        1938 Apr 6 -- autograph letter signed
      - Creston, Paul (Box 11, Folder 131)
        1938 Jul 18 -- card
      - Cumberworth, Starling A. (Box 11, Folder 131)
        1958 -- 2 autograph letters signed
      - Cushing, Charles C. (Box 11, Folder 131)
        1938 Sep 25 -- typed letter signed
      - De Loache, Benjamin (Box 11, Folder 132)
      - Diamond, David (Box 11, Folder 132)
        1938-1939 -- 5 typed letters signed
        1938 -- 3 cards
        1938 Feb 26 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Eastham, Clark (Box 11, Folder 132)
      - Etler, Alvin (Box 11, Folder 132)
        1938 Sep 7 -- telegram
        1933 Jul 9 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Evanti, Lillyann [one to E. Ames] (Box 11, Folder 132)
        1938 Jun 21 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - Fichandler, William (Box 11, Folder 133)
        1938 Sep 9 -- autograph letter signed
      - Fine, Vivian (Box 11, Folder 133)
        No year Sep 13 -- autograph letter signed
      - Finney, Ross Lee (Box 11, Folder 133)
        1938 Aug 15 -- autograph letter signed
        1938 Jul 25 -- typed letter signed
      - Forst, Rudolf (Box 11, Folder 133)
        1938 -- 4 autograph letters signed
      - Gideon, Miriam (Box 11, Folder 133)
        1938 Jul 14 -- typed letter signed
      - Gottlieb, Jack (Box 11, Folder 133)
      - Gray, Elsie (Box 11, Folder 133)
      - Green, Ray (Box 11, Folder 133)
        No date -- 3 autograph letters signed
        [one to Otto Luening]
      - Griffis, Ellis (Box 11, Folder 133)
        1938 -- 5 autograph letters signed
      - Harris, Roy (Box 11, Folder 134)
        [1938] -- 3 autograph letters signed [one to E. Ames; notations]
        1938 Sep 1 -- typed letter
      - Haufreucht, Herbert (Box 11, Folder 134)
        1938 Aug 24 -- card
      - Herzberg, Norman (Box 11, Folder 134)
        1938 -- 3 autograph letters signed
      - Holmes, Malcolm H. (Box 11, Folder 134)
        [1938] -- 2 typed letters signed
      - Hove, Mary (Box 11, Folder 134)
        1938 Sep 11 -- autograph letter signed
        1938 Oct 12 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Hull, Anne (Box 11, Folder 134)
        1938 Jul 11 -- typed letter signed
      - Katz, Paul (Box 11, Folder 135)
      - Keller, Homer (Box 11, Folder 135)
        1938 Jun 29 -- autograph letter signed
      - Korn, Richard K. (Box 11, Folder 135)
        1938 Sep 15 -- autograph letter signed
      - Labunski, Felix R. (Box 11, Folder 135)
        1938 -- 3 typed letters signed
      - Landau, Victor (Box 11, Folder 135)
      - Lapidus, George (Box 11, Folder 135)
        1938 -- 7 autograph letters signed
      - Leff, Ben (Box 11, Folder 136)
        1938 Aug 7 -- autograph letter signed
        1938 Aug 5 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Lewis, Merrills (Box 11, Folder 136)
      - Lieberson, Goddard (Box 11, Folder 136)
        typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Limpkin, Arthur Bennett (Box 11, Folder 136)
      - Lockwood, Normand (Box 11, Folder 136)
        1938 -- 2 telegrams
        1938 Sep 3 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Lubin, Ernest (Box 11, Folder 136)
        1938 Feb 5 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - McClosky, David Blair (Box 11, Folder 137)
        1938 Sep 2 -- typed letter signed
      - McCollin, Frances (Box 11, Folder 137)
        1939 Jul 10 -- typed letter signed
        1939 Jul 15 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - McIlheny, Hugh (Box 11, Folder 137)
        1938 Jul 21 -- typed letter signed
        1938 Jul 9 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Mamorsky, Morris (Box 11, Folder 137)
        1938 Jun 16 -- typed letter signed
      - Manners, Grace (Box 11, Folder 137)
        1939 Mar 19 -- typed letter signed [to E. Ames]
        1939 Mar 24 -- typed letter (carbon) from Elizabeth Ames to above
      - Maruchess, Alix Young (Box 11, Folder 137)
        1938 Mar 13 -- typed letter signed
        1938 Apr 8 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Miles, Harold (Box 11, Folder 137)
        1938 Aug 13 -- card
        1938 Aug 30 -- telegram
        1938 Aug 26 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Morris, Harold (Box 11, Folder 137)
      - Naginski, Charles (Box 11, Folder 138)
        No year Jul 18 -- autograph letter signed
      - Palmer, Robert M. (Box 11, Folder 138)
        1938 Nov 10 -- autograph letter signed
      - Parker, Muriel (Box 11, Folder 138)
      - Paulson, Herbert (Box 11, Folder 138)
        1939 Mar 19 -- typed letter signed
      - Pimsleur, Solomon (Box 11, Folder 138)
        1938 Aug 12 -- typed letter signed
      - Randegger, G. Aldo (Box 11, Folder 138)
        1938 Jun 19 -- card
        [to E. Ames, with enclosure of typed letter copy, dated 1938 Apr 24]
      - Rice, Charles P. (Box 11, Folder 138)
      - Rippell, Martha Mendenhall (Box 11, Folder 138)
      - Robins, Edna Grace (Box 11, Folder 138)
        1938 Aug 29 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Schmidt, Adolph (Box 11, Folder 139)
      - Schmitt, Homer (Box 11, Folder 139)
        No date -- 2 telegrams [rough copies]
        1938 Jul 26 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Schuman, William H. (Box 11, Folder 139)
      - Selby, John (Box 11, Folder 139)
      - Semiatin, Judah L. (Box 11, Folder 139)
        1938 -- 3 autograph letters signed [one to League of Composers]
      - Sevely, Jeno (Box 11, Folder 139)
      - Silberberg, Robert (Box 11, Folder 139)
        1938 Aug 27 -- telegram
      - Smith, Carleton Sprague (Box 11, Folder 139)
        1938 Apr 19 -- typed letter signed
      - Stackhouse, David Ludlow (Box 11, Folder 139)
      - Stevens, Halsey (Box 11, Folder 139)
        [1938] -- autograph letter signed
        1938 Sep 30 -- typed letter signed
      - Stoney, William (Box 11, Folder 139)
        1963 Jan 15 -- typed letter signed
      - Taylor, Adele W. (Box 11, Folder 140)
      - Tuthill, Burnet (Box 11, Folder 140)
        1937 Jul 25 -- typed letter signed
      - Wagner, Josef (Box 11, Folder 140)
        1938 -- 7 typed letters signed [one to E. Ames]
        1938 Sep 10 -- card
      - Wagner, Joseph (Box 11, Folder 140)
      - Walden String Quartet (Box 11, Folder 140)
        1938 Jul 16 -- autograph letter signed
      - White, Russell (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - Correspondence Concerning Yaddo Recordings, I.H.3
      - Allied Recording Products Co. (Box 12, Folder 141)
        1938 -- 5 typed letters signed
        1937-1938 -- 7 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Ames, Elizabeth (Box 12, Folder 141)
        1938-1946 -- 3 typed letters signed
        1938 Feb 10 -- telegram
        1937-1938 -- 8 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Bacon, Ernst (Box 12, Folder 142)
        1939 Oct 18 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Barrows, John (Box 12, Folder 142)
        1937 Oct 17 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Bennington College (Box 12, Folder 142)
        1937 Nov 11 -- 1 purchase order
        See also: Otto Luening
      - Bergen, Eugene (Box 12, Folder 142)
        1939 Jan 4 -- autograph letter signed
      - Brightenburg, Paul (Box 12, Folder 142)
        1937 Oct 5 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Brockway, Mrs. Tom (Box 12, Folder 142)
      - Buuck, Paul F. (Box 12, Folder 142)
        1938-1939 -- 3 autograph letters signed
      - Carnegie Corporation (Box 12, Folder 142)
        1938 Aug 17 -- typed letter signed
      - Clark Phonograph Record Company (Box 12, Folder 142)
      - Clarke, Henry Leland (Box 12, Folder 142)
        1938 Mar 15 -- typed letter signed
      - Creston, Paul (Box 12, Folder 142)
        1937-1938 -- 2 typed letters signed [one to E. Ames]
        1937 -- 3 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - De Blasius, Gio (Box 12, Folder 143)
        1937 -- 2 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - De Loache, Benjamin (Box 12, Folder 143)
      - Diamond, David (Box 12, Folder 143)
        1937-1939 -- 3 typed letters signed
        1937 Dec 2 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Duke, John (Box 12, Folder 143)
      - Etler, Alvin (Box 12, Folder 143)
        1939 -- 2 autograph letters signed
      - Ever-Ready Label Company (Box 12, Folder 143)
        1938 Aug 12 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Fairchild Aerial Camera Corp. (Box 12, Folder 143)
        1937 Aug 31 -- typed letter signed
      - Finney, Ross Lee (Box 12, Folder 143)
        1939 Aug 3 -- typed letter signed
      - Forst, Rudolf (Box 12, Folder 143)
        1939 Jan 3 -- autograph letter signed
      - Fujita, F. (Box 12, Folder 143)
        1948 Sep 27 -- typed letter signed
      - Goodman, Margaret (Box 12, Folder 144)
        1939 Jan 23 -- typed letter signed
      - Goslee, George (Box 12, Folder 144)
      - Greenberg, Gladys (Box 12, Folder 144)
        1939 Jan 29 -- autograph letter signed
      - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (H. Allen Moe) (Box 12, Folder 144)
        1937 -- 2 typed letters signed
        1937-1938 -- 2 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Heasty, John (Box 12, Folder 144)
        1939 Feb 28 -- typed letter signed
      - Hill, Martha (Box 12, Folder 144)
        1938 Jan 16 -- autograph letter signed
        1938 Jan 25 -- typed letter signed
        1938 Jan 22 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Charles W. Homeyer & Co., Inc. (Box 12, Folder 144)
        1938 Mar 23 -- typed letter
      - Jacobi, Frederick (Box 12, Folder 145)
        1937 Oct 13 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
      - KGGC Radio (San Francisco) (Box 12, Folder 145)
        1938 Sep 5 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Kendall, R. (Box 12, Folder 145)
        1939 Aug 26 -- typed letter signed
        1939 Sep 3 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Korn, Richard K. (Box 12, Folder 145)
        1939 Jan 5 -- typed letter signed
      - Lewis, Merrills (Box 12, Folder 145)
        1937-1939 -- 2 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Luening, Otto (Box 12, Folder 145)
        1937-1939 -- 2 typed letters signed
        1937 -- 9 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - McBride, Robert (Box 12, Folder 146)
        1938 Feb 7 -- autograph letter signed
        1937 Oct 11 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - McKay, Eugene (Box 12, Folder 146)
        1937 Dec 30 -- autograph letter signed
        1938 Jan 11 -- typed letter signed
      - Massinger, Charles (Box 12, Folder 146)
        1938 Sep 4 -- autograph letter signed [to E. Ames]
        1938 Sep 4 -- telegram
      - Mitchell, Mrs. E.K., Jr. (Box 12, Folder 146)
      - [Moore, Douglas ?] (Box 12, Folder 146)
        1937 Oct 23 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - The Music House (Box 12, Folder 146)
        1938 May 19 -- typed letter signed
      - The Music Room (Box 12, Folder 146)
      - New York Public Library (Box 12, Folder 147)
        1937 Dec 24 -- typed letter signed
        1937 Dec 28 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Pittaway, Rudolph (Box 12, Folder 147)
        1937 Oct 17 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Pro-Art Publications (Box 12, Folder 147)
        1939 Feb 11 -- typed letter signed
      - Quimby, Arthur (Box 12, Folder 147)
        1937 -- 3 typed letters signed
      - Rahm, Barbara (Mrs. Louis) (Box 12, Folder 147)
      - Robetor, Jo Ann (Box 12, Folder 147)
        1938 Sep 26 -- typed letter
      - Rood, Louise (Box 12, Folder 147)
        1937 Oct 10 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Sarah Lawrence College (Box 12, Folder 147)
        1938 Jan 21 -- typed letter signed
        1938-1939 -- 2 purchase orders
        1938 Jan 14 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Schmelzer, Helen Walling (Box 12, Folder 148)
        1938 Sep 26 -- typed letter (carbon) from E. Ames to above
      - Scott Radio Laboratories (Box 12, Folder 148)
        1938 -- 2 typed letters signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Skidmore College Library (Box 12, Folder 148)
        1939-1947 -- 3 typed letters signed
      - Skinner, Ernest M. (Box 12, Folder 148)
        1938 -- 3 typed letters signed [two to other people]
        1938 Mar 12 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
        1938 Feb 28 -- typed letter (carbon) from Marjorie Waite to above
      - Slade, Mrs. John (Box 12, Folder 148)
        1937 Oct 21 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Sly, Allan B. (Box 12, Folder 148)
        1937-1939 -- 4 autograph letters signed
        1939 -- 2 typed letters signed [one to Lois Porter]
        1937; No date -- 2 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Smith College (Box 12, Folder 149)
        1937 Nov 10 -- typed letter signed
      - Stern, Allan P. (Box 12, Folder 149)
      - Triest, Robert (Box 12, Folder 149)
        No year Dec 9 -- autograph letter signed
      - Tucker, Gregory (Box 12, Folder 149)
      - Tuthill, Burnet (Box 12, Folder 149)
        1937 Nov 2 -- typed letter signed
      - Vassar Cooperative Bookshop (Box 12, Folder 149)
      - Waite, Marjorie Peabody (Box 12, Folder 149)
        1937 Oct 25 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Wheeler, Rufus A. (Box 12, Folder 149)
        1939 Jul 31 -- typed letter signed
        1939 Aug 8 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Whitham, Earl (Box 12, Folder 149)
        1940 Aug 29 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Wuliger, David D. (Box 12, Folder 149)
        1939 Jan 20 -- autograph letter signed
      - Zenith Radio Corporation (Box 12, Folder 149)
      - Yaddo recordings (Box 12, Folder 150)
        4 lists
      - program/catalogs, tapes and recordings (Box 12, Folder 151)
        7 items
      - ledger book, record sales (Box 12, Folder 152)
    - Programs, I.H.4
      - Programs (Box 12, Folder 153)
        1933; 1936-1937
      - Program (Box 12, Folder 154)
        1938 -- 3 rough copies, broadcast materials, programs
      - Programs (Box 12, Folder 155)
        1951 -- 1 brochure
      - Music received (Box 13, Folder 156)
        1937-1938 -- 5 lists
        [1938] -- notes on rehearsals & informal performances of works
      - Yaddo Corporation members (Box 13, Folder 157)
        1963 May 8 -- list
        1937-38;1950-65 -- invitation lists
        [1938] -- drafts of invitation letters
      - Memos, minutes, reports (Box 13, Folder 158)
        1937-1938 -- 4 items
      - Memos, minutes, reports (Box 13, Folder 159)
        1940-1943 -- 9 items
      - Memos, minutes, reports (Box 13, Folder 160)
        1944-1947 -- 5 items
      - Memos, minutes, reports (Box 13, Folder 161)
        1950-1956 -- 7 items
      - Memos, minutes, reports (Box 13, Folder 162)
        1962-1963 -- 7 items
      - Memos, minutes, reports (Box 13, Folder 163)
        1964-1965 -- 10 items
      - Financial reports & balance sheets (Box 13, Folder 164)
        1940-1944 -- 8 items
      - Financial reports & balance sheets (Box 13, Folder 165)
        1945-1950 -- 5 items
      - Yaddo by-laws (Box 13, Folder 166)
        1 copy
        1942 Sep 1 -- contract between Yaddo and Harper & Brothers
        1933 Oct 10 -- 1 article appearing in Musical America vol. LIII, No. 15, p.1
        1938 Aug 14 -- 1 clipping, New York Herald Tribune
  - Yale Papers, I.I
    - Angell, Kay (Box 13, Folder 167)
      1958 Apr 22 -- autograph letter signed
    - Babini, Italo (Box 13, Folder 167)
      1959 Jan 8 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Bahlman, Dudley (Box 13, Folder 167)
      1958 Apr 14 -- autograph letter signed
    - Baldwin, Sherman (Box 13, Folder 167)
      1958 Apr 17 -- typed letter signed
    - Banks, J. Richard (Box 13, Folder 167)
      1954 Nov 8 -- typed letter signed
    - Barber, Julien C. (Box 13, Folder 167)
      1959 Jan 9 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Barber, Samuel (Box 13, Folder 167)
      1962 May 7 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
    - Barrows, John
      See: general correspondence; Yaddo
    - Bartholomew, Marshall
      See: general correspondence
    - Bassett, C.C. (Box 13, Folder 167)
      1958 Apr 30 -- autograph letter signed
    - Baumgartner, Hope Leroy (Box 13, Folder 167)
    - Bell, Whitfield J., Jr. (Box 13, Folder 167)
      1961; No date -- 2 autograph letters signed
      1954-1960; No date -- 4 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
    - Blum, John M. (Box 13, Folder 167)
      No year Apr 9 -- autograph letter signed
    - Borchard, Edwin M. (Box 13, Folder 168)
      1940 Mar 29 -- typed letter signed
    - Bozyan, H. Frank (Box 13, Folder 168)